A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Scholastic Achievement Dinner (T), June 21, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3775)
- Lincoln Fist Tower Dedication (Cancelled) - Rochester, New York, June 27, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3776)
- New York State Broadcasters Association Executive Conference - Cooperstown, New York, July 17, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3777)
- Staff Meeting, Rockefeller Foundation - New York City, July 25, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3778)
- Harlem State Park Opening - Bronx, New York, August 18, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3779)
- American Political Science Association Convention - New Orleans, Louisiana, September 5, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3780)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Convention - Concord, New York, September 6, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3781)
- Town Hall Luncheon - Los Angeles, California, September 11, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3782)
- National Study Commission - Washington, DC, September 13, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3783)
- Governor's Club Outing - Pocantico Hills, New York, September 14, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3784)
- Charles Sandman Jr. Fund Raising Dinner - Cherry Hill, New Jersey, September 17, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3785)
- Swearing In of Judges, St. Regis Hotel - New York City, September 19, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3786)
- Pro-American Professional Golfers Association (PGA) Gold Tournament (Cancelled) - Broome County, New York, September 19, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3787)
- Associated Industries - Lake Placid, New York, September 19, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3788)
- Italian American Legislature Club, Waldorf Astoria, September 21, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3789)
- Oakland County Republican Committee - Bloomfield Hills, Michigan, September 29, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3790)
- Museum of Primitive Art Exhibit - New York City, September 25, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3791)
- Project Hope Dinner - New York City, September 25, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3792)
- Executives Luncheon - Chicago, Illinois, September 28, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3793)
- Macomb County Republican Dinner - Mt. Clemons, Michigan, September 29, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3794)
- United Fund Meeting - Manufacturers Hanover Trust - New York City, October 1, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3795)
- Fund Raising for March, 812 Fifth Avenue - New York City, October 1, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3796)
- Water Pollution Control Federation Annual Conference - Cleveland, Ohio, October 3, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3797)
- Jane Wright Testimonial Dinner (Not Done) - Texas, October 6, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3798)
- Columbus Citizens Committee Dinner, Waldorf Astoria, October 6, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3799)
- New Opportunities for United State Foreign Policy, Sheraton Park - Washington, DC, October 6, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3800)
- Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry Breakfast - East Meadow, Long Island, New York, October 9, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3801)
- Vetrano Westchester Reception - Harrison, New York, October 12, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3802)
- Northern Westchester Hospital Dedication - Mt. Kisco, New York, October 13, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3803)
- Alfred E. Smith Dinner, Waldorf, October 18, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3804)
- Jewish Theological Seminary Installation - New York City, October 21, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3805)
- Skylab I Presentation on Rock and Flag to NAR, October 23, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3806)
- United Nations Day, Rockefeller Center - New York City, October 23, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3807)
- Nymrad - New York City, October 23, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3808)
- Trunk n' Tusk Dinner - Phoenix, Arizona, October 25, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3809)
- Arizona State University - Tempe, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3810)
- University of Arizona - Tucson, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3811)
- Trunk n' Tusk Dinner - Tucson, Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3812)
- Des Moines Republican Committee - Des Moines, Iowa, October 30, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3813)
- 25th Annual Students Conference on United States Affairs - West Point, New York, October 31, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3814)
- Histadrut Tribute Dinner for Senator Mathias (Cancelled) - Baltimore, Maryland, November 1, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3815)
- Swearing In of Howard Shapiro as State Commission of Investigation (SCI) Chairman - 270 Broadway, New York City, November 7, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3816)
- International Council Links Club - New York City, November 8, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3817)
- North Eastern Regional Conference Republican National Committee (T) - New York City, November 13, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3818)
- State Traffic Safety Council - New York City, November 14, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3819)
- Memorial Hospital Building Dedication - New York City, November 14, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3820)
- Foundation Luncheon Group - New York City, November 15, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3821)
- Family of Man Awards Dinner (Kissinger) - New York City, November 1, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3822)
- The Academy of Political Science Conference Columbia University - New York City, November 16, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3823)
- Trustees Luncheon - State University of New York, SUNY Albany - Albany, New York, November 21, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3824)
- South Mall Dedication - Albany, New York, November 21, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3825)
- University of North Dakota - North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3826)
- Luncheon - Grand Forks, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3827)
- Fund Raising Dinner - Minot, North Dakota, November 26, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3828)
- Citizens Union of the City of New York Honoring Al Marshall, American Hotel - New York City, November 27, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3829)
- Chamber of Commerce and Industry Meeting, Radio City Music Hall - New York City, November 28, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3830)
- B'Nai B'rith Anti-defamation League Dinner, Waldorf Astoria Hotel, November 29, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3831)
- Southern Republican Conference - Atlanta, Georgia, December 7, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3832)
- Institute for Adult Jewish Studies, Congregation B'nai Jeshurum - New York City, December 10, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3833)
- Appeal for Conscience Foundation "Man of Conscience Award" Pierre Hotel - New York City, December 11, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3834)
- Press Conference - Albany, New York, December 11, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3835)
- Meet the Press, December 16, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3836)
- Inauguration of Governor Malcolm Wilson, December 18, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3837)
- Republican State Committee, December 19, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3838)